National Organization for Women, New York State Chapter; Records apap029
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Subject Files, 1965-2011; 2; 22.17 cubic ft.
  - Chapter Information (2 of 2), 1976-1982 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Chapter Information, 1991-1995; 2000
  - Chapter Information and Websites, Undated (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Chapter Organization, 1972-1976 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Chapter Presidents Letter, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Chapter Questionnaires, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Chapter Renewal Mental Report, 1982-1984; 1988-1989 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Chapter Resources, 1974; 1979; 1983-1985; Undated (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Chapter Updates, 1989-1992 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Child Custody Issues, 1985-1987 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Child Custody Speak out, 1984-1986 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Child Rights Laws and Welfare, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Child Sexual Abuse, 1972; 1985-1989; Undated (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Child Sexual Abuse Working Together Towards Solutions- April 2, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Child Support, 1985-1988 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Child Support Standards Chair, 1989; 1992 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Childcare, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Childcare on College Campuses, 1988-1990 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Childcare Coordinating Council, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Childcare Initiative, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Choke x20- New York Celebration- July 5, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Citizen Co-Sponsor Driver, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Citizen Party, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Civil Rights, 2001-2002 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Civil Rights Abuse Complaint- Esther Shapiro, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Civil Rights Act- Talking Point, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Civil Rights Restoration Act, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Clarence Thomas Appointment Opposition Petition, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Coalition for Choice Participations Organization, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Coalition for Fair Domestic Relation Laws- Lobby Day, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Coalition of Freemen Transitions, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Coalition of Labor Union Women, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Comments on the Matrimonial Commissions Report, 2006 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Comments on New York State BAR Association Proposal for " No Fault Divorce", 2005 (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - Committee of Authorization or Non Authorization by Candidates, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - Committee on Examining Lawyers Conduct on Matrimonial Actions, 1993; Undated (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - Committee on Women Hearing, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Communications Team Report, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Community Access Program, Undated (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Comparable Worth: The Road to Pay Equality, Undated (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Complaints- Individual, 1987; 1988 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Compliance With Equal Employment Opportunities Act, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Comprehensive Employment and Training Act, 1979-1980 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Concerted Effort Inc., 1979 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Conference Call- Lois and Simone- February 4, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Conference Implementation Committee, 1981-1983 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Conference Minutes, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Conference Notes, 1992-1993 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Conference Racism, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Conference Resolution, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Conferences, 1973-1978; 1980-1981 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Confronting the Reality of Racism, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Congresswoman Pat Schroeder- President Campaign, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Connecticut Family Violence - Prevention and Response Act, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Connecticut NOW, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Consciousness Raising Task Force, 1980; 1981; 1990-1991; Undated (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Constitutional Equality Amendment (CEA) Workshop, 1995; Undated (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Contraception Conversations on Schools, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Controversy Over American Psycho, Undated (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Convener Authorization Forms, 1983; 1987 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Convener's Kit, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Convention Notes, Undated (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Convention Rules, 1986; 1989; 1993 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Conventions- Preparations (1 of 2), 1997-2002 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Conventions- Preparations (2 of 2), 1997-2002 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Cornell University Chapter, 1978-1979 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Correspondence- Incoming from Non-NOW Organizations, 1978-1982 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Correspondence- Outgoing to Non-NOW Organizations, 1978; 1981 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Correspondence- National Board, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Co-sponsor for HJ Res 1: ERA, Undated (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Council Policy, 1977-1983 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Counseling and Treating People of Color- 4th Annual Conference, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Court Case, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - COWLI Members, Undated (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Crank File, 1979-1982 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Crises Mail, 1978-1979 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Critical Choices and ERA March Poughkeepsie, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - Crunch! The Cost of Independence, 2000 (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - CT- NOW Leadership, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - Customer Service Complaints, 1989; 1991 (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - David Soares- PAC Questionnaire and Statements, 2004; Undated (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - Deborah Olick- 2008 NOW- New York State Legislator of the Year Award (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - Definitions, Undated (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - Definitions and Concepts for the Proposed Constitutional Equality Amendment for All Women, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - Delegate Complaints, Undated (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - Delegates, 1993; Undated (Box 4, Folder 50)
  - Delegates Unregistered, 2003; Undated (Box 4, Folder 51)
  - Delaware NOW, Undated (Box 4, Folder 52)
  - Democratic National Convention, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 53)
  - Democratic Platform, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 54)
  - Department of Education, 1986-1988 (Box 4, Folder 55)
  - Department of Health- Task Force Updates, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 56)
  - Department of Labor, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 57)
  - A Devoted Leader for Today Because our Future is NOW, Undated (Box 4, Folder 58)
  - Dialogues in Diversity, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 59)
  - Dignity for All Students Action Packet, 2001-2002 (Box 4, Folder 60)
  - Directory of Business and Professional Women, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 61)
  - Discrimination Complaints, 1984-1986 (Box 4, Folder 62)
  - Diversity Training/Resolution, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 63)
  - Division of Human Rights, 1977-1980 (Box 4, Folder 64)
  - Divorce and Child Custody Laws in New York State, 2008 (Box 4, Folder 65)
  - Divorce - Equitable Distribution and Other Financial Issues, 1984-1988 (Box 4, Folder 66)
  - Do it NOW (1 of 2), 1971-1977 (Box 4, Folder 67)
  - Do it NOW (2 of 2), 1971-1977 (Box 4, Folder 68)
  - Domestic Relations Law Task Force (1 of 2), 1978-1983 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Domestic Relations Law Task Force (2 of 2), 1978-1983 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Domestic Violence- Diane Pikful, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Domestic Violence and Domestic Relations: Proposed Legislation, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Dont Assume I Don't Cook: Recipes for Women's Lives, Undated (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Draft of Suggestions for New Chapter Spokesperson, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Due Transmittal Forms, 1977-1980 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Dues Rebate Statements, 1985-1991 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - East End Chapter, 1978-1980 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Eastern Region State Coordinator, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Economics of Divorce, Undated (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Education (1 of 3), 1965-1983 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Education (2 of 3), 1965-1983 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Education (3 of 3), 1965-1983 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Education Task Force, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Eleanor Roosevelt - Community Service Award, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Eleanor Smeal- Women and Power on Campus in Politics, and Work, Undated (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Election Committee, 1988; 1992 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Elections, 1974-1975; 1998 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Elections- National NOW, 1974; 1977-1978 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Elections- New York State Executive Committee, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Elections- New York State NOW, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Elizabeth Holtzman Campaign for District Attorney, 1980-1981 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Elizabeth Cady Stanton- Seneca Falls, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Emergency Contraception OTC- Organizing Packet to NOW Chapter Leadership, Undated (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - EMH, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - The Empire State Pride Agenda- May 3-7, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Employment, 1968-1973; 1982-1985; Undated (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Employment Manual, Undated (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Employment Task Force (1 of 2), 1977-1978 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Employment Task Force (2 of 2), 1977-1978 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Ending the ERA of "Childless Mothers", Undated (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Ending Violence Against Women, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Endorsement - New York Attorney General Robert Abrams, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Engaging Women's Power and Strength for the 21st Century, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Engle Bright/ Tully Brest Cancer/ Pesticide Registration Efforts Meet with Success in Joint Assembly/ Senate Agreement- June 24, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Equal Marriage Update: Hawaii and Alaska, Undated (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Equal Rights Amendment (1 of 2), 1978-1979; 1984; 1988 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Equal Rights Amendment (2 of 2), 1978-1979; 1984; 1988 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Equal Rights Amendment- Betty Friedan, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Equal Rights Amendment - Countdown Campaign, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Equal Rights Amendment- Discrimination Complaints, 1984-1986 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Equal Rights Amendment Emergency Key- DU Alpert, 1978-1979 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Equal Rights Amendment Grassroots Discussion Committee, 1994-1995 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Equal Rights Amendment Legislative Intent Committee Report- June 19, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Equal Rights Amendment:- PAC- NOW- New York State, 1984-1987 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Equal Rights Amendment- Vermont, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Equal Rights Amendment- Walk-A-Thon, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Equality Action Fund- October 19, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Equality Countdown Campaign, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Erie County Suburban Chapter, 1973-1974 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Evan Davis- Attorney General, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Eve-o-lution: Women Through the Ages, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Every Women Coalition, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - An Examination of the Washington State Parenting Act, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Executive Committee Correspondence, 1975-1976 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Executive Committees, 1984; 1988-1992 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Exempt Tax Form Information- January 10, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Exhibitor's Agreement, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Expense Guidelines For Executive Committee and Task Force Chairs- January 18, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Expense Vouchers, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Expenses, 1994; Undated
  - FACS, 1989-1991; 1993 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Fact Sheet- Parental Consent, Undated (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Facts About Pay Equality, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Facts on Reproductive Rights: A Resource Manual, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Facts on Women, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Fair Speech: Gender Neutral Language, Undated (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - False Prophets, Sales Premises, and False Advertising, Undated (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Family Violence, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - Fast Forward - Women Take Charge, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - Federal Executive Order #11246aa, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - Federal Incumbent Re- Endorsement Worksheet, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - Feminist Campaign Image, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - Feminist Candidate Recruitment, Undated (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - A Feminist Contact with America: Organizing NOW for the Future, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 44)
  - Feminist Ethics of Leadership, Undated (Box 6, Folder 45)
  - Feminist for Free Expression, Undated (Box 6, Folder 46)
  - Feminist Forum Series, 1991-1996 (Box 6, Folder 47)
  - A Feminist Perspective on the Ethics of Leadership, Undated (Box 6, Folder 48)
  - Feminization of Poverty, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 49)
  - Feminization of Power, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 50)
  - Field Team Report, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 51)
  - Fight the Rights '95- NOW- New York State Annual Membership Convention, 1994-1996 (Box 6, Folder 52)
  - Fighting Bum out, Undated (Box 6, Folder 53)
  - Finances, 1979-1981 (Box 6, Folder 54)
  - Financial Crisis Resolution, 2001 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Financial Position- October 31, 2005 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Financial Report Summary, 2004 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Financial Reports, 1989-1990 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Financial Statements and Supplemental Data, 1993-1997 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Finger Lakes, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - First A Woman - A Conference on Relationships for Women with Disabilities, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Five Women, Undated (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Five Year Report of the New York Judicial Committee on Women in Courts, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Florida's 1990 College Feminist Unity Conference (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Flyer- Join NOW- New York State Young Feminist Task Force, Undated (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Ford and Nasser, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Forms, 1970; 1974 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Forward Ever Backward Never- Achieving Political and Economic Party, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Foundation Meeting, Undated (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Frances Conion - Treasurer Resignation, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Freedom of Choice Act Update, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Freedom on Our Terms, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - From There To Here and N.O.W, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Fundraising, 1980-1983 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Fundraising- Direct Mail, 1982; Undated (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Fundraising is Fundamental, Undated (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Fundraising Ideas, 1982-1983 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Fundraising- National Fundraising Telephone Socialization Kit, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Fundraising- New York City, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Fundraising- "Pork Roast", 1984 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Fundraising- Presidents Phone Solicitation, 1980-1981 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - The Future Women in Political- Fundraiser, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - General Announcements, 1970-1974 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - General Information for Members, 1976-1980 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - General Information and Questions, 1984-1988 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - General Publications List, Undated (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - General Updated, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Genesee Valley- Rochester, 1974; Undated (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - George J. Hochbrueckner, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Get Together to Feminize Power, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - Ginny Montes- Farewell as National Secretary, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - Glens Falls, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - Global Conference, 1991-1992 (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - Gloria Bernstein- National NOW Action Center, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - Gloria S. Jacobs Speech, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - Gloria Steinem- The American Family and the Future of Feminism- October 21, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - God's Country: A Case Against Theocracy, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - Good New, Bad News, and Shoes, Undated (Box 7, Folder 44)
  - Gordan Amabch- Commissioner of Education and President of SUNY, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 45)
  - Gotham NOW- Resolution, Undated (Box 7, Folder 46)
  - Governor U.L. Carey- Endorsement, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 47)
  - Government Relations Report, 1991; 1996-1997 (Box 7, Folder 48)
  - Greater Rochester NOW, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 49)
  - Greater Syracuse NOW, 1980-1982; 1987; 1989 (Box 7, Folder 50)
  - Greg Camp NOW Scandal, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 51)
  - Grievance: Alpert vs Larsen, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 52)
  - Growing Your Grassroots- Membership Recruitment and Retention, Undated (Box 7, Folder 53)
  - Guidelines for Candidate Interviews and Endorsements, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 54)
  - Guidelines for Women's Leadership Support Groups, Undated (Box 7, Folder 55)
  - Hai Misrock- Response to Keynote Speaker, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 56)
  - Handbook on Child Support Enforcement, Undated (Box 7, Folder 57)
  - Harriet Newman Cohen and Adrina S. Hillman Testimony on Matrimonial Actions, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 58)
  - Hartford Workers Compensation and Employment Liability, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 59)
  - Hazel Varner- Sex Discrimination Case, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 60)
  - Health- New York State Healthcare Campaign, 1990-1991 (Box 7, Folder 61)
  - Helpful Websites, Undated (Box 7, Folder 62)
  - Hillary Clinton- 160th Anniversary of the First Women's Rights Convention- November 8, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 63)
  - Hilary Clinton and Sarah Palin, The Impact of Gender on Mobilization of Female Voters in the 2008 Presidential Election, 2010 (Box 7, Folder 64)
  - Hiring, 1984-1985 (Box 7, Folder 65)
  - HIV Testing, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 66)
  - Hofstra University School of Law: Max Schmertz Distinguished Professorship Lecture- "Beware Some Words Of Caution About Divorce Meditation", 1995 (Box 7, Folder 67)
  - Homelessness by Dorce (Women and Children), 1984-1985 (Box 7, Folder 68)
  - Honoring Generations of Women- Senator Hillary Clinton, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 69)
  - Hope v. Perales (1 of 2), 1990-1991 (Box 7, Folder 70)
  - Hope v. Perales (2 of 2), 1990-1991 (Box 7, Folder 71)
  - HPV Vaccine Hearing, 2007 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Human Rights Davison, 1982-1984 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Huntington NOW Officers and Board Members, 1986-1988; 1992 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - The Illegitimacy Ratio, Undated (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Images of Elizabeth Holtzman, 1990; Undated (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Inaugural Protest, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Info Directory of Women Professionals, Businesses and Services, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Information for Chapters, 1975-1976 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Information on Candidates, Undated (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Insurance, 1984-1988 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Insurance- Background, 1982-1985 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Insurance Liability, 1984-1985 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Insurance- NOW vs Metropolitan Life, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Insurance - New York State Code, 1985-1986 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Insurance and Pension- Sex Discrimination, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Intern Handbook- August 24, 2001 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - International NOW Correspondence, 1980-1981 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Internship Candidates, 200-2003 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Internship Participation Forms, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Intrepid Awards Gala, 2005; 2008 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Insurance- NOW vs Mutual of Omaha, 1984-1986 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Is it Race or Gender?- Presidential Panel- Black Law Student Association and Students for Reproductive Justice- March 11, 2008 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Issues Forum with Senator George G. Mitchell, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Issue Hearing on Economic Rights, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Issues and The Actions Clearing House Plan, Undated (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - It's Your Choice- Candidates, Undated (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Jacquelyn A Partridge- Veterans, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Jamestown, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Janet Black - Follow-up on Workshops, Undated (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Jean Sasson- Speaker, Undated (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Jefferson City, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Jennifer Erland- Winner of NOW- New York State Young Feminist Task Force Essay Contest- October 27, 2007 (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - Join NOW, 1997-1998 (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - Job Training Partnership Act (1 of 2 ), 1982-1984 (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - Job Training Partnership Act (2 of2 ), 1982-1984 (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - Jobs With Justice, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - Joseph Porto, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - Judge Anthony Kennedy, 1987 (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - Judy Goldsmith: Breakfast (NOW National President), 1985 (Box 8, Folder 39)
  - Judy Gragam- Business Manager (1 of 2), 1974-1976 (Box 8, Folder 40)
  - Judy Gragam- Business Manager (2 of 2), 1974-1976 (Box 8, Folder 41)
  - Justice at Last- Mazierski Loses, Undated (Box 8, Folder 42)
  - Justice For Women- Eliminating the Statue of Limitations on Rape, Undated (Box 8, Folder 43)
  - Karen Bernstein, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Kathryn Lake Mazierki- Candidate for President, Undated (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Klein and Broderick Court Case, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - The Knolls, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Korn/Ferry International Position Specification, Undated (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Kris Moody- New Hampshire NOW Chapter President, 2002 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - KSB Schedule, Undated (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Labor Law #220, Undated (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Lan Cao, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Latino-American Committee, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Lawsuits, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Leadership Lists, 1984; 1987-1992 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Leadership Updates, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - League of Women Voters, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Legal Docket- NOW Legal Defense and Education Fund, 1997-1998 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Legal Policy and Guide, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Legal Referral Services- General Questionnaire, Undated (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Legal Recourse Kit- Sexual Harassment in Housing, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Legal Rights Workshop, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Legislation (1 of 2), 1984; 1986-1988 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Legislation (2 of 2), 1984; 1986-1988 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Legislative Achievements for Women in NYS- 20 Year Retrospect, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Legislative Agenda Changes, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Legislative Office, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Legislative Program, 1983 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Leonard Stavinsky, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Lesbian and Gay Discrimination Survey, Undated (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Lesbian Rights, 1978-181 (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Lesbian and Gay Rights- AIDS, 1986-1987 (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Lesbian and Gay Rights: Bias Towards Beach, 1987-988 (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Lesbian and Gay Rights: Civil Rights Bill, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - Lesbian and Gay Rights: Correspondence, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - Lesbian and Gay Rights: Employment Contract- Joan Butcher, 1984 (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - Lesbian and Gay Rights: Foster Care, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - Lesbian and Gay Rights: Fundraising, 1984-1987 (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - Lesbian and Gay Rights: Hate Crimes Statistic Bill, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - Lesbian and Gay Rights: Housing, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - Lesbian and Gay Rights: Lobbyist Reports, 1986-1987 (Box 9, Folder 38)
  - Lesbian and Gay Rights: Local Ordinances, 1984; 1986 (Box 9, Folder 39)
  - Lesbian and Gay Rights: New York City Executive Order #22, 1984 (Box 9, Folder 40)
  - Lesbian and Gay Rights- NOW Job Descriptions, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 41)
  - Lesbian and Gay Rights: Special Project Reports, 1987-1988 (Box 9, Folder 42)
  - Lesbian and Gay Rights: Memos, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 43)
  - Lesbian and Gay Rights: Target State Proposal, National NOW Veatch Program, 1985-1986 (Box 9, Folder 44)
  - Lesbian Rights: Brochures, Undated (Box 9, Folder 45)
  - Lesbian Rights: Summit, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 46)
  - Let's Begin the Celebration- Rochester Chapter, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 47)
  - Letter for Help From NOW- RESTRICTED, Undated (Box 9, Folder 48)
    Conditions Governing Access
    Must consult an archivist before viewing these materials.
  - Letters Sent to Oprah- RESTRICTED, Undated (Box 9, Folder 49)
  - "Lib"- The All-Purpose Scapegoat, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 50)
  - List of Candidates - Westchester, 1992 (Box 9, Folder 51)
  - List of Council/PAC Meetings, 1986-1996 (Box 9, Folder 52)
  - Litigation Report, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 53)
  - Liverpool, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 54)
  - "Living the Legacy"- Celebrating the 150th Anniversary of the Women's Rights Movement, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 55)
  - Liz Holtzman Defense (Box 9, Folder 56)
  - Lobby Days, 1981-1983; 1995; 1997-1998; 2007; 1979 (Box 9, Folder 57)